{
  "category1": {
    "topic": "Highs and Lows",
    "question1": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 100,
      "question": "Ocarina of Time, Twilight Princess Sales",
      "answer": "OoT, 14MM vs 10MM"
    },
    "question2": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 200,
      "question": "McDonalds, Starbucks Locations",
      "answer": "Starbucks, 15.2k vs 13.5k "
    },
    "question3": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 300,
      "question": "Asia, North America GDP",
      "answer": "Asia, 39.8 vs 34 trillion USD"
    },
    "question4": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 400,
      "question": "Africa, South America GDP",
      "answer": "South America, 4.2 vs 2.8 trillion USD"
    },
    "question5": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 500,
      "question": "M*A*S*H, My Little Pony Friendship is Magic Episode Count",
      "answer": "MASH, 256 vs 230"
    },
    "question6": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 600,
      "question": "U15 boy, open female powerlifting total",
      "answer": "Female, 1620.4 vs 1592.8 lbs"
    }
  },
  "category2": {
    "topic": "Topic 2",
    "question1": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 100,
      "question": "Question 1",
      "answer": "Answer 1"
    },
    "question2": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 200,
      "question": "Question 2",
      "answer": "Answer 2"
    },
    "question3": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 300,
      "question": "Question 3",
      "answer": "Answer 3"
    },
    "question4": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 400,
      "question": "Question 4",
      "answer": "Answer 4"
    },
    "question5": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 500,
      "question": "Question 5",
      "answer": "Answer 5"
    },
    "question6": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 600,
      "question": "Question 6",
      "answer": "Answer 6"
    }
  },
  "category3": {
    "topic": "Topic 3",
    "question1": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 100,
      "question": "Question 1",
      "answer": "Answer 1"
    },
    "question2": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 200,
      "question": "Question 2",
      "answer": "Answer 2"
    },
    "question3": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 300,
      "question": "Question 3",
      "answer": "Answer 3"
    },
    "question4": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 400,
      "question": "Question 4",
      "answer": "Answer 4"
    },
    "question5": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 500,
      "question": "Question 5",
      "answer": "Answer 5"
    },
    "question6": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 600,
      "question": "Question 6",
      "answer": "Answer 6"
    }
  },
  "category4": {
    "topic": "Topic 4",
    "question1": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 100,
      "question": "Question 1",
      "answer": "Answer 1"
    },
    "question2": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 200,
      "question": "Question 2",
      "answer": "Answer 2"
    },
    "question3": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 300,
      "question": "Question 3",
      "answer": "Answer 3"
    },
    "question4": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 400,
      "question": "Question 4",
      "answer": "Answer 4"
    },
    "question5": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 500,
      "question": "Question 5",
      "answer": "Answer 5"
    },
    "question6": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 600,
      "question": "Question 6",
      "answer": "Answer 6"
    }
  },
  "category5": {
    "topic": "Topic 5",
    "question1": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 100,
      "question": "Question 1",
      "answer": "Answer 1"
    },
    "question2": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 200,
      "question": "Question 2",
      "answer": "Answer 2"
    },
    "question3": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 300,
      "question": "Question 3",
      "answer": "Answer 3"
    },
    "question4": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 400,
      "question": "Question 4",
      "answer": "Answer 4"
    },
    "question5": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 500,
      "question": "Question 5",
      "answer": "Answer 5"
    },
    "question6": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 600,
      "question": "Question 6",
      "answer": "Answer 6"
    }
  },
  "category6": {
    "topic": "Topic 6",
    "question1": {
      "double": true,
      "value": 100,
      "question": "Question 1",
      "answer": "Answer 1"
    },
    "question2": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 200,
      "question": "Question 2",
      "answer": "Answer 2"
    },
    "question3": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 300,
      "question": "Question 3",
      "answer": "Answer 3"
    },
    "question4": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 400,
      "question": "Question 4",
      "answer": "Answer 4"
    },
    "question5": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 500,
      "question": "Question 5",
      "answer": "Answer 5"
    },
    "question6": {
      "double": false,
      "value": 600,
      "question": "Question 6",
      "answer": "Answer 6"
    }
  }
}
